Quiz = {
    1 : {
        "Question" : "What is the name of Han Solo's ship?",
        "Answer" : "The Millennium Falcon"
    },
    2 : {
        "Question" : "Where did Obi-Wan take Luke after his birth?",
        "Answer" : "Tatooine"
    },
    3 : {
        "Question" : "Who is Emperor Palpatine's Granddaughter?",
        "Answer" : "Rey"
    },
    4 : {
        "Question" : "Who was Anakin Skywalker's padawan?",
        "Answer" : "Ahsoka Tano"
    },
    5 : {
        "Question" : "What is the name of Boba Fett's ship?",
        "Answer" : "Slave 1"
    },
    6 : {
        "Question" : "Who killed Qui-Gon Jin?",
        "Answer" : "Darth Maul"
    },
    7 : {
        "Question" : "Who built C-3PO?",
        "Answer" : "Anakin Skywalker"
    },
    8 : {
        "Question" : "Per Yoda, what is the path to the dark side?",
        "Answer" : "Fear"
    },
    9 : {
        "Question" : "Bo-Katan wanted what from Moff Gideon in the Mandalorian?",
        "Answer" : "The Darksaber"
    },
    10 : {
        "Question" : "What color is Mace Windu's lightsaber?",
        "Answer" : "Purple"
    }
}